Dorcas Olaniyan Frontend Developer

≥ olaniyandorcas91@gmail.com

**** 07069637222

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/dorcas-olaniyan-114228143 https://github.com/Mhizdhee

Profile

Driven and enthusiastic web developer with a strong passion for creating user-friendly, beautiful and exceptional web experiences. I'm proficient in Html, Css, TailwindCss, Javascript, React.js, Materia UI, Chakra UI,Git and GitHub. I'm committed to staying up to date with latest trends and technologies to ensure the best user experience. I possess good communication skill, hardworking, ability to work individually and as part of a team, with commitment to continuous learning and professional growth.

Education

2018 – 2019 Lagos, Nigeria	Master of Business Administration (MBA) University of Lagos
2010 – 2015 Ogun, Nigeria	Food Science and Technology (BSC) Federal University of Agriculture Abeokuta

Professional Experience

2022/10 - present Lagos, Nigeria

Frontend Developer

Stutern (Stutern Graduate Accelerator)

- 1. Collaborated with the design team to implement user interfaces (UI) and user experiences (UX) using React.js, Tailwind CSS, and Material UI and translated design mock-ups or wireframes into functional web pages.
- 2. Implemented a modular components architecture using React, allowing for code reusability and faster development iterations across multiple projects.
- 3. Writing and maintaining clean, efficient, and well-documented code, debugged and troubleshooting issues that may arise during development or testing.
- 4. Collaborating with other team members, including designers, and backend developers, to understand project requirements and deliver high-quality front-end solutions.
- 5. Used version control systems like Git to manage code repositories and collaborate with other developers.

2022/04 - 2022/08 Lagos, Nigeria

Frontend Developer (Internship)

a Zuri Team, Inc

- 1.Developed user interfaces for web applications.
- 2. Collaborated with the design team to implement user interfaces (UI) and user experiences (UX) using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- 3.Ensured that web applications are responsive and accessible across different devices and screen sizes using responsive design techniques, media queries, and mobile-first development principles.

Skills

HTML	• • • •	CSS	• • • •
JavaScript	• • • • •	React	• • • • •
Tailwind Css	• • • • •	Material UI	• • • • •
Chakra UI	• • • • •	GIT	• • • • •
GITHUB	• • • •		